<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Psycasts Expanded - Hemosage</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, Taranchuk, Reann Shepard, Sir Van</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</packageId>
			<displayName>Royalty</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
			<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VPsycastsE</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Psycasts Expanded</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2842502659</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VPE.Hemosage</packageId>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VPsycastsE</li>
		<li>vanillaexpanded.achievements</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>Vanilla Psycasts Expanded - Hemosage introduces a brand new Psycaster path that can be selected if Vanilla Psycasts Expanded is found - hemosage. A hemosage utilises the power of hemogen to control the battlefield, and the abilities are focused on magnifying the strength of a sanguophage.
Hemosage has access to a number of new psycasts that consume hemogen instead of generating psychic heat. Initiate blood focus to rapidly regenerate psyfocus, lob blood shards and sanguine spears at your enemies, vomit a thick mist of blood at your enemies causing them to go into vomiting spree, or force your enemies to give you the offering of blood. At the final level, you can open the skipgates to the ancient sanguophage place, generating a downpour of blood, greatly enhancing your psycasting capabilities.
With a new deathrest meditation focus, you can now build a meditation platform in your deathresting chambers, enhancing the XP gain of your psycaster.
Works perfectly with Vanilla Races Expanded - Sanguophage.
This mod requires Biotech DLC, as it relies on Sanguophages and Hemogen resource.</description>
</ModMetaData>